asweetpeachef.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy • A Sweet Pea Chef

## How We Collect and Use Information

 **Personally Identifiable Information:**  We collect information that can be used to identify you as an individual (“Personally Identifiable Information”) only when you provide such information directly to us in connection with the Service.

You aren’t required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information in order to use our website; however, you may choose to provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us such as your first and last name, ZIP code and email address in response to optional prompts featured on our website. We may also retain the contents of any messages you send to us or through the Services or website, and we may collect information you provide in User Content that you post to the Services or website. If you elect to make a donation or purchase merchandise through the Service, you may also provide us or a trusted third-party provider with the financial information required to process and fulfill your transaction. Finally, we may now or in the future allow Users to create accounts. If you choose to sign up for a User account, we may collect certain Personally Identifiable Information, including your username, first and last name, phone number, and email address. If you sign up for our email newsletter, we will collect your email address.

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of the Service, including the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting feature. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Service, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to visiting the Service. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to maintain and improve the Service, and we may share anonymous statistical information from our use of Google Analytics with our business partners for such purposes. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Service, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Service is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html), and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Service by disabling cookies on your browser. In addition, if you want to prevent your data from being provided to Google Analytics, you can [learn how to opt out using a Google plug-in](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

When you visit the website, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Sweet Pea Chef enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us or our business partners to track your usage of the Service or website over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

## How We Store and Protect Your Information

 **Storage and Processing:**  Personally Identifiable information collected on the website may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Sweet Pea Chef maintains facilities. Sweet Pea Chef may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Sweet Pea Chef or its subsidiaries, affiliates, or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you, including Personally Identifiable Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Keeping your information safe:**  Sweet Pea Chef cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. However, Sweet Pea Chef cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Sweet Pea Chef or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of Sweet Pea Chef’s distributors, such as social networks. Sweet Pea Chef is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

## Advertising

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, one of which is [http://www.gourmetads.com](https://www.gourmetads.com/). These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

## Children’s Privacy

Sweet Pea Chef does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at lacey@sweetpeachef.com.

## Links to Other Websites and Services

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible for and do not control any third parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third party access to your User Content, you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from sources other than through the Service.

For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit [http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy](https://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of a sweet pea chef then you may contact us at lacey@sweetpeachef.com

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Sweet Pea Chef may, in its sole discretion, modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner, we will update the “last modified” date at the bottom of this page.

Last updated August 15th 2015
